 Μανουσάκη Οινοποιία – NOSTOS WINES


Clear deep dark red colour with a purple hue. Rich,dense legs. Intense nose with ripe juicy black fruits and some caramelized notes. Velvet tannins in this big bodied wine, warm finish with crunchy dark fruit. Bitter chocolate and a hint of eathiness. Long aftertaste that lingers for at least a couple of minutes. Drink now but can age up to 12-13 years.

Χρώμα Κρασιού
Κόκκινο

Κατηγορία ως προς την περιεκτικότητα σε αζύμωτα σάκχαρα
Ξηρός

Ποικιλίες Κρασιού
Mouvedre