Μανουσάκη Οινοποιία – NOSTOS WINES


Clear bright red with rusty edge in colour. Intense rustic nose with dried fruits, ripe berries and some nutty character. Medium bodied with smooth tannins, warm finish with bitter chocolate, notes of nuttiness, and a herbacious finish. Very long finish. Drink now, can be aged 5-6 more years.

Χρώμα Κρασιού
Κόκκινο

Κατηγορία ως προς την περιεκτικότητα σε αζύμωτα σάκχαρα
Ξηρός

Ποικιλίες Κρασιού
Ρωμέικο , Μαντηλάρι
